foreign
[Music]
plan on the go with the Manulife mobile
app save time and access your benefits
card right from your phone
the Manulife mobile app allows you to
view and download your benefits card to
your mobile device
to do so log in to the Manulife mobile
app and select benefits card from the
main navigation from there you can
choose to add to Apple wallet or save it
to your phone by taking a screenshot
if accessing from an Android device
download the wallet passes app from the
Google Play Store prior to loading your
benefits card
then select add to wallet process
now your benefits card will be available
from your mobile device or if you have a
smart watch you'll be able to view your
benefits card right from your wrist
and your life makes managing your
benefits easy and secure